buildingregisterevolution.com 2016-06-25

# THE BR NETWORK PRIVACY POLICY ("PRIVACY POLICY")

THE BR NETWORK PRIVACY POLICY ("PRIVACY POLICY")
BR Network Limited “BR Network") recognises the importance of protecting the personal information and the
privacy of data provided by You and that may personally identify You which We collect in connection with Your
use of any BR website ("Website") and the services offered on the Website ("Services") referred to in this policy
as ("Personal Data").
Why We ask you for Your Personal Data
What data We ask You to provide and when
How to contact Us for further information
How We use Your Personal Data
How We use Your email and IP address Partner Sites
Do We use Cookies?
Advertising on Our Website
How can you change, correct or update Your Personal Data?
How to Close Your user Registration
Why We ask you for Your Personal Data
We ask You for Your Personal Data to allow You to use the Services most effectively and for Us to work on Your
behalf to develop BR Network for You by making available services which are relevant to You.
We ask that You provide Us in return with some information about You to enable Us to meet this objective. We
may ask You for additional information from time to time and will store this information with the data We already
keep about You. You may change, update or remove it at any time in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
What data We ask You to provide and when
BR Network will always notify You as to the types of Personal Data and any other information We are collecting
about You as well as the uses that BR Network intends to make of such information. When You complete Our
registration process We will collect Your full name, address, email address and such other relevant information
as We may state in the registration from time-to-time. We may collect data which tracks how You use the
Website and Services.
How to contact Us for further information
Your questions regarding Our Privacy Policy should be directed to the BR Network site co-ordinator who will be
pleased to assist You with any questions or problems You might have: please contact him here.To return to the
BR Network home page please click here.
How We use Your Personal Data
We will only use Your Personal Data to improve Your use of Services, the quality and relevance of any
communications We send to You and the Website itself.
Except as We state in the Privacy Policy, We do not sell, rent or provide third parties with any of the information
comprised within Your Personal Data that enables You to be personally identified.
BR Network does however, collect certain non-personally identifiable information about You, such as the number
and types of sessions and transactions that You make Using the Website and Services. Such information is
usually aggregated with that collected in respect of all users of the Website and Services in the form of general
demographic or geographic statistical information about the numbers and types of products and services that all
users of the Website and Services may browse. These statistics may be collected in respect of specific partners.
Only such non-personally identifiable information is ever made available by BR Network to third parties and never
Your Personal Data that identifies You such as Your name, address, financial details or email address.
Disclosure of your Personal Data
We may disclose Your Personal Data to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate
holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.
We may disclose Your Personal Data to third parties:
     •    In the event that We sell or buy any business or assets, in which case We may disclose Your Personal
          Data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
     •    If BR Network Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case
          personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.

      •   If We are under a duty to disclose or share Your Personal Data in order to comply with any legal
          obligation, or in order to enforce or apply any of the terms of our User Terms and our Conditions or
          Conditions for the Supply and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Ours, our
          customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for
          the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
	  
How We use Your email and IP address
BR Network uses Your email address primarily to contact You in the way We have described and for the
administration of the Website. If however You do not wish receive emails that We send for information or
marketing purposes please notify Us by email.
We may use the IP address log to determine where users of the Website are located and where problems such
as accessing the Website may have originated.
Any statistical information is aggregated on an anonymous basis about all users of Our Website. This statistical
information may be used by BR Network to help Us develop enhanced services as part of the Website and
Services for Our users and to determine which elements of Our Website are being used most effectively. This
data will only be used by BR Network to offer categories of users relevant products or services We develop
specifically for them.
The information provided by You in relation to Your log-in and user identity is, subject to the statements made
above, unique to You and viewable only by Us and by You.
From time to time We may confirm Your email address by sending an email to the email address which You have
registered. We may also from time to time as required send registered users an email message containing
information about updates to the Website, the Services, or in accordance with the BR Network User Terms.
Additionally, We may contact You via Your email address in the event that We need to inform You of any issues
or problems with the Website, the Services or any specific transaction carried out by You.
	  
Partner Sites
We believe that the statements We make in this Privacy Policy should always apply to You. However some of the
services made available to You may mean that You leave the Website, and where You enter another website it
will not be possible to apply Our Privacy Policy.
	  
Do We use Cookies?
The Website may use small pieces of data know as “cookies”. Cookies are set on Your browser when You log-in
to the Website and We use cookies to identify users on the Website. Cookies enable Us to remember Your log-in
and password so You do not have to remember it and re-enter it each time You visit Our Website. BR Network
cookies cannot be read or used by any other Websites and do not contain Your Personal Data.
	  
Advertising on Our Website
We may use an advertising company to display banner advertisements on Our Website. These advertisements
may contain cookies. While We may use cookies on other parts of Our Website, We do not have access to the
information stored on cookies received with banner advertisements.
	  
How can you change, correct or update Your Personal Data?
We aim to keep the information We keep about You up to date and We will change any of the information We
keep about You at any time when You notify Us by email at admin@brnetwork.com
	  
How to Close Your user Registration
If You wish to cease Your use of the Website You may close Your BR Network membership by notifying Us by
email. We will withdraw the information held by Us about You from the BR Network database.
In any case where We have the right to terminate Your use of BR Network, We will confirm by email to You that
Your BR Network User registration has been closed.
BR Network recommends that You review this Privacy Statement periodically as BR Network may update it from
time to time with the aim of ensuring that You are fully informed of Our use of Your Personal Data.
BR Network Limited
2nd Floor
Whatman House
St Leonards Road
Allington
Maidstone
Kent.
ME16 0LS
Tel: 01622 662668
Fax: 01622 609409
